how are we gonna find four thousand
dollars in six hours we're broke poor we
have to peddle our wares who has where
someone you know we don't have wares we
live in a ramshackle shanty house shanty
house slash office
[Applause]
maybe we should spend money advertising
so more people will see the website do
we only have a hundred dollars
for advertising or like for the whole
company
yes
your video production company is called
video production company i don't like
your tone what do you call that it's
just a stapler it doesn't need a fancy
name this is a computer mouse
we've only filmed one of the seven
seances i'm sorry but i just don't have
the money then we can't help you i got
you is this powdered sugar
[Music]
make your nightmares a reality
i mean the fog and everything is very
ominous but i would hate to assume
because here at sales solutions we take
office safety
very
seriously
[Applause]
how'd it go
you're all doomed